Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9 Locals, 2.
  - Local 926
    - Local 926 Incoming Sarah McClure Correspondence, December 30, 1940-November 17, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Beal Regarding Contracts, Decca Conference and Factionalism, December 29, 1941; 4.
      - Beal Regarding Decca Conference and Contract, January 20, 1942; 5.
      - William Chapman Regarding Decca Conference, January 11, 1942; 6.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 30, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Constitution, October 24, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 25, 1942; 9.
      - James Matles Regarding Officers, July 1, 1941; 10.
      - Matles Regarding Contract, December 4, 1941; 11.
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Negotiations, November 17, 1942; 12.
    - Local 926 Outgoing Sarah McClure Correspondence, July 20, 1940-March 12, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Sarah McClure to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, July 20, 1940; 1.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, October 12, 1940; 2.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Bonding, October 30, 1940; 3.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, April 19, 1941; 4.
      - McClure to James Matles Regarding Officers and Factionalism, June 21, 1941; 5.
      - McClure to UE Regarding Officers and Factionalism, July 16, 1941; 6.
      - McClure to UE Regarding Constitutions, October 22, 1941; 7.
      - McClure to Matles Regarding Contracts and Factionalism, November 11, 1941; 8.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 11, 1941; 9.
      - McClure to Sidney Gilbert Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, February 2, 1942; 10.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Negotiations, February 23, 1942; 11.
      - McClure to Neil Brant Regarding Factionalism and Decca Conference, March 8, 1942; 12.
      - McClure to Matles Regarding Dues and Decca Conference, March 9, 1942; 13.
      - McClure to UE Regarding Unemployment, April 22, 1942; 14.
      - McClure Telegram to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, November 2, 1942; 15.
      - McClure to Matles Regarding Negotiations, November 7, 1942; 16.
      - McClure Telegram to Matles Regarding Decca Conference, November 16, 1942; 17.
      - McClure to Matles Regarding Negotiations and War Labor Board, March 12, 1943; 18.
    - Local 926 Incoming Correspondence, May 28, 1941-November 6, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Julius Emspak to Joe Baker Regarding Finances, March 5, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Charlotte Dyke Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 28, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Vivian Houser Regarding Political Action Committee, October 15-November 6, 1947; 3-4.
      - James Matles to Charles Jones Regarding Managament, May 28, 1941; 5.
      - Matles to Baker Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, October 6, 1941; 6.
      - Matles to Fern Martin Regarding Staff Members, August 9, 1943; 7.
    - Local 926 Outgoing Correspondence, June 8, 1941-May 22, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Joe Baker to James Carey Regarding Negotiations, June 8, 1941; 1.
      - Baker to James Matles Regarding Working Conditions, October 3, 1941; 2.
      - Baker to Matles Regarding Finances and Factionalism, February 23, 1942; 3.
      - Charlotte Dyke to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 19, 1943; 4.
      - Dyke to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 19, 1945; 5.
      - Dyke to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, April 17, 1946; 6.
      - Dyke to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, August 28, 1946; 7.
      - Fred Higgins to Matles Regarding Grievances and Supervisors, May 17, 1941; 8.
      - William Ingalls to Emspak Regarding Disbanding, January 17, 1949; 9.
      - Charles Jones to Matles Regarding Supervisors, May 22, 1941; 10.
      - Helen Klemann to Matles Regarding Dues and Factionalism, March 9, 1942; 11.
      - Fern Martin to Matles Regarding Grievances and Supervisors, July 30, 1943; 12.
      - Evla Roverts to UE Regarding Factionalism, July 20, 1943; 13.
      - Roy Shaffer to Matles Regarding Grievances and Supervisors, June 4, 1941; 14.
      - Catherine Wilson to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 5, 1943; 15.
    - Local 926 Correspondence, May 2, 1979-May 30, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Local 926 Charter Supplies, May 9, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Local 926 Leaflets, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - "District Announces New Contract" Leaflet, 1940; 1.
    - Local 926 Organization, November 18, 1939-January 13, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - James Pascoe to Robert Connor, November 18, 1939; 1.
      - Pascoe to Robert Cowdrill, November 18, 1939; 2.
      - Cowdrill to Pascoe, November 24, 1939; 3.
      - Pascoe to Decca Records, November 24, 1939; 4.
      - Pascoe to James Matles, November 27, 1939; 5.
      - Matles to Pascoe, November 27, 1939; 6.
      - S. Kelly to Matles, December 1, 1939; 7.
      - Pascoe to Connor, December 5, 1939; 8.
      - Memo, December 1939; 9.
      - Pascoe to Matles, December 1939; 10-11.
      - Matles Telegram to Pascoe, December 11, 1939; 12.
      - Matles to Pascoe, December 15, 1939; 13.
      - Pascoe to Matles, December 17, 1939; 14.
      - Matles to Pascoe, December 28, 1939; 15.
      - Charter Application, January 13, 1940; 16.
    - Local 926 Officers, June 17-24, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Memo, June 21, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Gardner, July 17, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Edwin Beal, July 24, 1941; 3.
    - Local 926 Factionalism and War Labor Board Case, August 5-September 8, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram to John Gojack, August 5, 1943; 1.
      - John Gojack to Fitzgerald, August 10, 1943; 2.
      - Gojack Telegram to Fitzgerald, August 12, 1943; 3.
      - James Conroy to Fred Gardner, September 8, 1943; 4.
    - Local 926 Disbanding and Recharter, January 20-October 8, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Merle Bennett to Julius Emspak, October 8, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, January 20, 1949; 2.
      - Gojack to Emspak, January 21-May 6, 1949; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Gojack, May 9, 1949; 5.
  - Local 927
    - Local 927 Officers Lists, January 1941-August 1950 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Local 927 Incoming Correspondence, February 6, 1940-August 9, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Julius Emspak to Howard White Regarding Organization, February 6, 1940; 1.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Organization and Factionalism, February 23, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Frank Lung Regarding Organization and Factionalism, February 23, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Richard Patz Regarding Seperate Charter and Local 917, April 6, 1940; 4.
      - Emspak to Patz Regarding Local 917, May 10, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Transfer Cards, November 27, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Albert Buckgren Regarding Factionalism, February 16, 1950; 7.
      - James Matles to White Regarding Contracts, March 21, 1940; 8.
      - Matles to White Regarding Union Label and Microphone Industry, October 15, 1940; 9.
      - Matles to White Regarding Negotiations, February 4, 1942; 10.
      - Matles to White Regarding Contracts, March 19, 1942; 11.
      - Matles to Buckgren Regarding Political Action, August 9, 1950; 12.
      - A.N. Towsen to White Regarding Government Contracts, November 19, 1940; 13.
      - Unsigned Letter to White Regarding Military Personnel, August 21, 1942; 14.
    - Local 927 Outgoing Correspondence, May 1939-December 1950 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Hazel Albright to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Arbitration, Firings and Factionalism, February 11, 1949; 1.
      - Albert Backgren to Julius Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, February 7, 1950; 2.
      - Backgren to James Matles Regarding Shure Brothers, April 2-14, 1950; 3-4.
      - Backgren to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 3, 1950; 5.
      - Backgren to Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1950; 6.
      - Mildred Bybee to UE Regarding Officers and Dues, January 16, 1944; 7.
      - Kathleen Carpenter to Emspak Regarding Officers, August 6, 1942; 8.
      - Inez Hyatt to UE Regarding Unemployment, Seniority and Factionalism, January 24, 1945; 9.
      - Marjorie Mitchell to UE Regarding Overtime, May 11, 1943; 10.
      - Mitchell to UE Regarding Wages, May 5, 1944; 11.
      - Richard Patz to Emspak Regarding Local 917 and Factionalism, April 11, 1940; 12.
      - Leo Tschechettin to Emspak Regarding Officers, April 1, 1940; 13.
      - Howard White to Matles Regarding Seperate Charter, May 3, 1939; 14.
      - White to A. R. Khan Regarding Negotiations, October 10, 1939; 15.
      - White to Matles Regarding Contracts, March 18, 1940; 16.
      - White to Matles Regarding Union Label and Conscription, October 13, 1940; 17.
      - White to Matles Regarding Microphone Industry, Wages and Government Contracts, October 16, 1940; 18.
      - White to Matles Regarding Government Contracts and Company Statement, November 8, 1940; 19.
      - White to Emspak Regarding United Steelworkers of America Transfers, November 12, 1940; 20.
      - White to Matles Regarding Wgaes and Microphone Industry, January 14, 1941; 21.
      - White to Emspak Regarding Officers, Women and Government Contracts, February 10, 1942; 22.
      - White to Matles Regarding Contracts, March 16, 1942; 23.
      - White to Emspak Regarding Contracts and Military Services, August 12, 1942; 24.
    - Local 927 Per Capita Reports, March-July 1940 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Local 927 Seperate Charter, April 4, 1939-February 23, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - James Matles to Howard White, April 4, 1939; 1.
      - William Yager to James Matles, January 23, 1940; 2.
      - Matles to Yager, January 29, 1940; 3.
      - Charter Application, February 2, 1940; 4.
      - White to Julius Emspak, February 2, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to Yager, February 6, 1940; 6.
      - White to Emspak, February 11, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak to Yage, February 23, 1940; 8.
    - Local 927 Shure Brothers Organization, April 10-October 8, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - James Matles to William Sheehan, April 10, 1950; 1.
      - Sheehan to David Mates, April 12, 1950; 2.
      - Matles to Sheehan, August 9-October 8, 1950; 3-4.
    - Local 927 Correspondence, July 15, 1943-January 10, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - John Gojack to James Matles Regarding Wages and War Labor Board, July 15, 1943; 1.
      - Gojack to Matles Regarding Wgaes, Contract and Microphone Industry, April 26, 1946; 2.
      - David Scribner Richard Marhanka Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 10, 1951; 3.
  - Local 928 (Hartford City)
    - Local 928 (Hartford City) Officers Lists, October 1947 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Local 928 (Hartford City) Dues Check-off Letters, February 7-November 17, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Local 928 (Hartford City) Organization, August 10, 1946-August 20, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Elizabeth Moore to Julius Emspak, August 10, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Moore, August 19, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, August 19, 1946; 3.
      - Moore to Emspak, August 20, 1947; 4.
  - Local 928 (Fort Wayne)
    - Local 928 (Fort Wayne) Incoming Correspondence, August 16-September 12, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - James Carey Telegram to Lester Fuhrer Regarding Negotiations, August 16, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Don Graham, September 12, 1940; 2.
    - Local 928 (Fort Wayne) Outgoing Correspondence, August 1940-May 1948 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Lester Fuhrer Telegram to James Carey Regarding Organization, August 16, 1940; 1.
      - Thelma Johnson to UE Regarding Disbanding, May 1948; 2.
    - Local 928 (Fort Wayne) Strike Bulletin, September 4, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Local 928 (Fort Wayne) Organization, June-September 1940 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Charter Application, June 17, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to James Pasco, June 20, 1940; 2.
      - Arthur Meloan to James Carey, August 16, 1940; 3.
      - Meloan Telegram to James Matles, August 20, 1940; 4.
      - Carey to Meloan, August 20, 1940; 5.
      - Memo, September 1940; 6-7.
  - Local 929
    - Local 929 Officers Lists, September 1947-January 1955 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Local 929 Incoming Correspondence, November 7, 1947-February 9, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Myers Regarding Finances, February 9, 1948; 1.
      - Russ Nixon to Myers Regarding Political Action Committee, November 7, 1947; 2.
    - Local 929 Outgoing Correspondence, December 6, 1946-July 31, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Ruth Daniels to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, July 31, 1953; 1.
      - Fred Myers to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, December 6, 1946; 2.
      - Myers to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 20, 1947; 3.
    - Local 929 Organization, December 12, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Rice, December 12, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, December 12, 1946; 2.
    - Local 929 Inter-union Rivalry, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Petitions, 1956; 1.
      - Bob Friend to Jim, November 1956; 2.
      - Memo, March 19, 1957; 3.
  - Local 929 (Marion)
    - Local 929 (Marion) Incoming Correspondence, June 25, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - Edwin Beal to Laster Bragg Regarding Peerless Organization, June 25, 1942; 1.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Outgoing Correspondence, February 19-20, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - Doris Berger to UE Regarding Staff Members, February 19, 1941; 1.
      - Ruby Hussong to UE Regarding Staff Members and Organization, February 20, 1941; 2.
      - Ruth Slagle to UE Regarding Staff Members, February 19, 1941; 3.
      - Minnie Whirl to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 19, 1941; 4.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Leaflets, 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Earl Weimer to Farnsworth Employee Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, September 1-11, 1939; 1-2.
      - "Wages?" Regarding Organization, May 1940; 3.
      - "Attention" Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, 1940; 4.
      - "CIO Runes Out" Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 5, 1941; 5.
      - "Dear Delta Worker" Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 1941; 6.
      - "Dear Friend" Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 1941; 7.
      - "Dear Farnsworth Worker" Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 14, 1941; 8.
      - "Flash" Regarding Delta Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, March 1941; 9.
      - "UE-CIO News Bulletin" Regarding Delta Organization, April 1941; 10.
      - "Delta Workers to Vote" Regarding Delta Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 1941; 11.
      - "That Old Red Herring Again" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 1941; 12.
      - "Strike Rumors" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, April 1941; 13.
      - "Let's Compare" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, May 1941; 14.
      - "Meeting Tonignt" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 15.
      - "IBEW-AFL News" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 16.
      - "Night Shift" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 17.
      - "Facts not Fiction" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 18.
      - "IBEW News" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 19.
      - "IBEW News" Regardign Farnsworth and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 20-21.
      - "A 10 Cent Per Hour Raise" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 22.
      - "Announcing" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 23.
      - "IBEW News" Regarding Delta and IBEW, 1941; 24.
      - "They Call This Americanism" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 25.
      - "A Vote for the UE is a Vote for You" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 26.
      - "To the Women of Delta" Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 27.
      - UE Farnsworth News Regarding Organization, 28.
      - "Why Wait" Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 29.
      - "Attention Farnsworth Employees" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 30.
      - "The Issue" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 31.
      - "Be Prepared" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 32.
      - "Ft. Wayne Farnsworth Chose the UE-CIO" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 33.
      - "Vote No" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 34.
      - "Vote No, Defend the IBEW", 35.
      - "Attention All Workers of the Farnsworth Plant" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 36.
      - "Why the AFL In Marion" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 37.
      - "Marion UE News" Regarding Organization, 38.
      - "To All Workers At The Farnsworth Plant" Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 39.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Pamplets, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Dear Delta Worker Regarding Delta and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 28, 1941; 1.
      - Plain Talk With the Electrical Worker Regarding IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 2.
      - An Open Letter Regarding Delta and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, 1941; 3.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Newspaper Clippings, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - "Strike Parley Held at Plant", February 20, 1941; 1.
      - "The Dawn of a New Era", December 13, 1940; 2.
      - "Electrical Workers Win Closed Shop", 1941; 3.
      - "Radion Factory Payroll Here Tops $250,000", 4.
      - "Labor is Worst Enemy", 5.
      - "Manufacturing Leaders To Tour Delta Electric", 6.
      - "CIO Attacks AFL Proposal", 7.
      - "Waner Gear Hit By Strike", 8.
      - "Committee On Americanism", 9.
      - "Foreman's Club To Be Organized", 10.
      - "Radio Plant Open House Plans Pushed", 11.
      - "Radio Plant Open House Draws Crowds", 12.
      - "Marion Hospitality", 13.
      - "Radio Officers to be Guests Here", 14.
      - "Radio Factory Orders Total One Million", 15.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Marion Times, March 29, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Local 929 (Marion) Organization, March 28, 1941-March 26, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - George Faulk to Julius Emspak with Newspaper Clipping, March 28, 1940; 1.
      - Charter Application, June 1940; 2.
      - Radio Program with January 2, 1941, William Chambers Letter to James Matles, January 1941; 3.
      - Edwin Beal to Matles, January 9, 1941; 4.
      - Russell Tomlinson Telegram to Matles, January 9, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Beal, March 10, 1941; 6.
      - Beal to Emspak, March 14, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to Beal, March 24, 1941; 8.
      - Beal to Emspak, March 26, 1941; 9.
      - Petition, 1941; 10.
    - Local 929 (Marion) Correspondence, April 28, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Merle Bennett to Julius Emspak Regarding Fighting Fund, April 28, 1952; 1.
  - Local 930 (Charlotte)
    - Local 930 (Charlotte) Officers Lists, November 25, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Local 930 (Charlotte) Incoming Correspondence, September 25, 1941-May 14, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Julius Emspak to Bruce Barrett Regarding Finances and Offices, September 25, 1941; 1.
      - James Matles to Hazel Cook Regarding Staff Members, April 13-May 14, 1942; 2-3.
    - Local 930 (Charlotte) Outgoing Correspondence, November 1941-March 1942 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Wayne Alldaffer to UE Regarding Organization, November 1941; 1.
      - Bruce Barrett to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Officers, September 23, 1941; 2.
      - Hazel Cook to Emspak Regarding Organization and Unemployment, January 1942; 3.
      - Cook to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Organization and Officers, March 27, 1942; 4.
      - James Fairchilds to Emspak Regarding Organization, December 30, 1941; 5.
      - James Farzier to Emspak Regarding Organization, Factionalism and Officers, February 11, 1942; 6.
      - Donald Raines to James Matles Regarding Organization, January 1942; 7.
    - Local 930 (Charlotte) Financial Secretary's Report, October-December 1941 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Local 930 (Charlotte) Organization, March 8, 1941-March 9, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - Charter Application, March 7, 1942; 1.
      - James Pascoe to Julius Emspak with Leaflets, March 8, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Pascoe, June 10, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Walter Barry, December 3, 1941; 4.
      - Barry to Emspak, December 8, 1941; 5.
      - Report of Local 930, 1941; 6.
      - James Frazier to James Matles, March 24, 1942; 7.
      - Frazier to Emspak, March 26, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Frazier, April 6, 1942; 9.
      - Frazier to Emspak, April 14, 1942; 10.
      - Frazier to Al Loehn, April 19, 1942; 11.
      - Fred Gardner to Emspak, May 28, 1942; 12.
      - Emspak to Gardner, June 5, 1942; 13.
      - Gardner to Emspak, October 19, 1942; 14.
      - Emspak to Gardner, October 30, 1042-March 9, 1943; 15-16.
  - Local 930 (Richmond)
    - Local 930 (Richmond) Officers Lists, July 1948-May 1949 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Local 930 (Richmond) Incoming Correspondence, March 30, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Julius Emspak to Edna Nichols Regarding Organization, March 30, 1948; 1.
    - Local 930 (Richmond) Outgoing Correspondence, March 4, 1948-September 8, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Edna Nichols to Julius Emspak Regarding Hug Organization, March 4, 1948; 1.
      - Nichols to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Finances, July 24, 1949; 2.
      - Nichols to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Negotiations, September 8, 2949; 3.
    - Local 930 (Richmond) Seperate Charter, December 3, 1947-March 30, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Charter Application, December 3, 1947; 1.
      - Reece Warmoth to James Matles, December 3, 1947; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Kirkwood, December 5, 1947; 3.
      - William Parker to Emspak, January 12, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to John Gojack, January 16, 1948; 5.
      - Gojack to Emspak, January 21, 1948; 6.
      - Parker to Emspak, February 23, 1948; 7.
      - Emspak to Gojack, February 25, 1948; 8.
      - Gojack to Emspak, March 8, 1948; 9.
      - Emspak to Gojack, March 17, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Reece Warmoth, March 30, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to Gojack, March 30, 1948; 12.
    - Local 930 (Richmond) Negotiations, August 31-October 10, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Julius Emspak to John Gojack, August 31-October 10, 1949; 1-2.
  - Local 931
    - Local 931 Officers Lists, February 4, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Local 931 Officers Lists and Supplies, April 2, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Local 931 Membership Resolution, May 1944-March 1948 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Resolution Regarding Grievances, May 1944; 1.
      - Resolution Regarding Factionalism, March 14, 1948; 2.
    - Local 931 Incoming Correspondence, February 19, 1942-December 12, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Bill Cahn to Leo West Regarding Publicity, June 9, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Chet Brunke Regarding Mine Mill Strikes, February 19, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to John Erickson Regarding Overtime, January 11, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Frank Marutz Regarding Staff Members, August 30, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Marutz Regarding Organization, October 13, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Ralph Williams Regarding Dues and Veterans, October 30, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Walter Casebier Regarding Finances, January 19, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Don Hotchkin Regarding Finances, April 16-July 24, 1945; 8-9.
      - Emspak to Hotchkin Regarding Strikes, October 24, 1945; 10.
      - Emspak Telegram to Normal Hardy Regarding Officers, July 19, 1946; 11.